I got a new silicone cat suit from Rania and it's a special one again.
It's quite heavy because there are boobs and butt.
It's textured and it has a special color which I created together with Rania.
And I'm going to try it on for the first time today.
And I also have a special styling plan so let's go.
Alright, I put some more makeup on and I decided to go full reptile look and go with the snake makeup.
Or at least snake look-alike fantasy makeup, I don't know.
The old trick, use a fishnet tights and put it over your head and then just dab down different shades of green and black and highlighter.
that's what I did here and also I put in some contact lenses obviously. Green I
thought about going for snake slit contact lenses but decided to just use
normal green ones because I think the color matches really well with the color
of the suit. Speaking of the suit... this is the suit! So this is the textured green
reptile silicon suit and I said green is a color I figured out together with
Rouanier so they asked me about hey what color do you want and I was like hey
green like a nice metallic green and you can buy that color now in their shop so
you should check out the description text I put the link down there also my
discount code so if you want to have that too you can order it another special
feature is this airbrush color here so we have colorful accents to say like a
second pattern with the black outlines here and the lighter green in the middle
so even more colorful and the 3d yeah look-alike and I think it's really nice
I tried to replicate that with my makeup with light green and a bit of black if
If you want to acquire about another custom color, please write to the customer service.
They can help you.
Also, if you have specific questions regarding sizing, please write to the customer service.
And the back side does not have this airbrush pattern, but I can turn around.
This is the back side and there is a hole in the butt.
Why? No one knows.
And this is the standard version.
So if you don't want to have this hole in the backside, then please write to the customer service.
If you want to have zippers in your suit, please write to the customer service.
This is a standard size.
So they only have this one size.
And it's supposed to be unisex.
Though I have to say it feels like it runs smaller than the usual one size catsuits.
I have a black one and a pink one from them.
And I think it's smaller.
So I'm 173 centimeters tall and weigh round about 57 kilogram.
Check the size chart, ask the customer service if you're not sure.
It is really stretchy but if you're not sure ask them.
Also it is a neck entry catsuit so yes I squeezed in through this neck.
That's why it's called neck entry catsuit.
I have another video in which I show how I undress a silicone catsuit I have a video in which I show
how I dress a neck and latex catsuit which is basically the same process so you can have
a look at these they're on my channel and if I can give you one tip use enough lube so to dress
these silicone suits you should use water-based lubricant and a lot of lube always helps a lot
So I really use so much by now that I have no problems sliding into the suits and it feels really slippery.
But it makes life so much easier if you just use an ungodly amount of lube.
I do have a small package from Morania which came with the suit because actually the suit has a second piece.
Which is this mask.
It's a silicone mask also with the spray paint again. Matchy matchy, no eyes, no mouth.
So this would be the look with the mask. When Roya said they wanted to send the
Reptile pattern I was like yeah yeah I can finally do like a snake makeup and
then I said yeah but I should definitely show the mask because a lot of their
customers want to wear masks and all of this together to have the full look and
the full enclosure. I'm not going to wear the mask. It would be too big for me because it is
one size again and I reckon it's suitable for head circumferences from 58 centimeters on. There are
holes in the nose and there are one two three four five six six tiny holes in the eyes.
So I think you can see something through them otherwise there wouldn't be any holes.
and because I also want to show you or tell you something about boots they are filled with cotton
so compared to the silicone boobs they are really lightweight and they do feel comfortable so a
question I also got asked if are they hollowed out or are they pushing down my own real boobs
and no they're not hollowed out but they're not too restrictive they are not pushing down my own
boob so it does not feel uncomfortable. I already set up my light for taking a few pictures and
photographs. What I also wanted to tell you is that the silicone is four millimeter thick and
the suit weights over four kilogram so this is something you do notice after a while or at least
I notice it I can feel the weight on my shoulders on the back of my shoulder blades but otherwise
it is perfectly comfy because it's so stretchy and it is compared to latex because that's also
always the question that gets asked how does it feel compared to latex it is thicker it feels
more squishy but it also feels more enclosing so it's not the same as latex but it is similar
and if you like latex chances are good that you like silicone as well if you have a latex allergy
this can be a great alternative because it's not latex so yeah if you want to give it a try as i
I will link all the stuff in the description text where you can also find my discount code and
Links to my other socials because if you want to check them out go for it
I also upload always a lot of behind the scenes stuff and additional pictures on my patreon
so if you want to see more then check that out too and
if you have any questions leave them in the
comments, I also made a
FAQ video about silicone you can also check that one out with a pink silicone suit I had friends
over trying silicone for the first time so there are basically a lot of silicone videos I should do
a playlist for all the silicone videos so yeah I think that's it I am going to take a few pictures
now which you can find on my socials so I hope you enjoyed this video I hope you like my look
tell me if you did and I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye